Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying robes drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting.
Either way, I'm feeling alive!
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high.
Hail a brand new dawn!
Blaze across the sky!
Time to journey on.
On your mark.
Camel of other things.
Well, on Earth, a legendary.
Hooray!
If you can show your breath,
Then we'll make some waves.
We run our daunted.
Ain't no beginners!
Cause if you want it,
Then you're a winner!
For we are on the cruise,
And freedom is the only rule!
Fearless night and day!
Cause that's just our way!
Find one piece!
I'll be the first!
I heard it be so bad, I could burst!
It's all this real!
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel!
I'm done playing, filled with the waiting.
In a world I'm feeling
alive, but I'll be loud!
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far!
Gotta make it to the end!
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind!
I've always got your back, my friend!
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward!
Dreaming from the very
first day I'd make my name!
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed!
I'm done playing through with the wave!
In every world I'm feeling alive!
Look out below!
Wake up, sunshine!
And here we go!
We go!
Ryugu Kingdom, come in!
This is the Border Patrol.
A large, badly damaged ship is seeking
emergency entry into the country.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Just do your job and let them in.
It's a little complicated, sir.
It belongs to...
Oh, Celestial Dragon!
In what?
King Neptune!
Wait, are you sure?
Where's the entry?
Send a rescue team right away!
I'll go welcome them myself.
I don't know he may!
What in the world is a celestial
dragon doing on the seafloor?
I can't believe this is happening.
Must have been attacked by
a sea king or something.
Here's what I don't get.
They hate us fishmen, right?
So what were they doing sailing
through such deep water?
Let's help, you idiots!
My whole worthless crew
just had to go and die!
Bring me a mask, you vulgar fishes!
I can't tolerate your fish man's stench!
I demand that you bring me a mask!
I need you to save my life, filthy fools!
This creep's got zero respect for us.
He thinks we're going to help
him talking to us like that?
Doctor, now!
I need help! Are the medics here?
Well, yeah, they're here, but they're
not sure if they want to help that thing.
Put him out of his misery.
He doesn't deserve to live.
He's pure scum.
Sounds like something's
going on at the harbor.
Hey, it's a celestial dragon.
Oh, man.
Looks like a world noble's causing this.
Well, that's interesting.
I guess his ship got wrecked, and now
he's flipping his lid or something.
Come on, let's go check it out.
This is guaranteed to be
good for a few laughs.
This is not how events
were supposed to unfold.
The fishman slaves have been
allowed to return to their island?
How can this be? Daddy dear!
It's bureaucracy, my son.
The fishman pirate Jimbe
joined the seven warlords.
Then he brokered a deal.
But I don't understand!
Jimbe was the captain of the sun pirates,
the lowly thugs who'd
been hiding the slaves.
He negotiated to have their
evasion charges dropped
and obtained amnesty for
the slaves to return home,
you see.
But if that's the case, then
they aren't just any slaves.
Some of them are probably my
slaves, right, Daddy dear?
Oh, I'm certain of it, my son.
It turns my stomach to
think they're living a
free and easy existence after
disrespecting us. Fine, then.
I'll just have to hunt them
down and reclaim them, won't I?
It's only right,
considering how much money I spent on
collecting those slaves in the first place.
It's not fair.
This should be easy.
Why didn't anyone tell me the
seafloor was so unhospitable?
Hey, what do you guys think you're doing?
What?
Long time no see, Hamio's guard.
How dare you address me without my title?
You're all my slaves!
My personal property you
must return with me at
once do you hear I didn't
permit you to run free
Wait don't do it you guys he's a celestial
dragon it'll avoid the
amnesty if you kill him
Put that gun down know
your place you belong to me
and you will do as I say I'm your
master Your master! Up on the surface,
all you have to do is cry and the admirals
will come running to you
at the drop of a hat.
You realize that's the only reason
people are scared of you nobles.
But you're at the bottom
of the sea floor right now.
As long as the islanders stay
quiet, and trust me, they will.
Whatever happens to you, they'll
think it was an accident.
Hey, he's got a point there.
I'll keep my mouth shut.
Me too! Moms the one!
Just look at that creep!
He's barely even alive!
I might as well get it
over with right now.
No, make it real slow.
He should suffer the same
way that you guys did.
Kill him.
Make him suffer.
Don't give him any mercy. What? What?
I thought everyone respected me.
I can't forgive you.
Not after what you did.
Not until my dying day.
No!
Don't do it!
Shoot him!
On this life!
Don't do it!
You're just stupid fiend!
Queen Otolime!
Oh, no, they shot the queen!
Queen Otohime, I...
Everyone, drop your guns at once.
Look around, children are watching.
Aladdin, I heard about
the Celestial Dragon.
Where is he now?
Not sure.
I just got here myself.
Boss Jinbe!
Have you seen our mother?
She rushed out of the palace.
To come down here? Hey, brother.
These Celestial Dragons, who are they?
They're not like us.
They're humans.
Humans?
Not all humans in the
world are bad, but these...
Are not to be trusted.
I heard some gunshots right
when I got here. Let's go.
Queen of Tohime.
It only grazed me.
Why are you protecting him?
You have no idea what kind of
pain that man inflicted on us.
The hell he put us all through.
He treated us like we were nothing
more than a bunch of animals.
I know.
I can feel the anguish in your hearts.
I do not question that.
Has mother been injured? Oh, no!
I know it's difficult.
But you can't pollute the children's
minds with your anger towards humans.
Your resentment.
Do not make it theirs.
They deserve the chance to meet
humans and make up their own minds.
Please you can't tell them you have to
hold it in our tragedy and our hatred?
They must die with us
they were one in the same!
You stay still your
majesty what is this? No!
No!
What the?
THE SEA KING! No!
What the hell?
just happened.
That was no coincidence.
Shura Hachi, are you the one who did this?
Wow, Captain, you're really freaking out.
The legend my family spoke
of for all those years.
A mermaid gifted with mysterious powers.
An almost supernatural ability that
allows her to summon and control.
the sea kings.
I scoured the sea floor
searching for the truth.
Searching for traces on a stable mermaid.
My family was right.
Their dream was true.
I found her.
You think Shirahoshi's
the legendary mermaid?
I knew you'd find her, Captain. Shush.
No one else can find out about this.
It's a secret legend so
old that everyone has
forgotten about it
except for My family so I
suspect can you imagine
if I could get the sea
kings to do my bidding
not a person alive could
stop me I could do
anything and take anything
I wanted so what's the
next step in the plan
are we gonna kidnap
princess Shirahoshi or what
of course not I simply
have to make her my wife
you do realize she's still only a
child don't you yeah that's the problem
Aladdin
I'll treat him if you wish my
queen It's the right thing to do
I'll take care of your wound next
A few weeks later Once the
celestial dragon's health
was stable enough for him
to travel home He prepared
to disembark for his voyage
But queen otohime did
something rather unexpected
before he could leave
You will pay for this you damn fish you
insulted and humiliated
me despite the fact that
I'm a respected world
noble your actions were
unforgivable and you
will come to regret them
so we just saved his life
and then he turns around and
threatens us He's got some
nerve speaking to us that way.
We provided him with a
ship and a crew to go home.
What the hell else does he expect from us?
We shouldn't even be
letting him leave anyway.
He's a danger to the whole island.
Wait a minute.
It's evident to me that
you have more to say.
So I'll travel to the world
above with you to hear you out.
She can't.
It's too dangerous.
Please don't go. Mother, no.
You must reconsider.
I cannot allow you to face such danger.
If you truly wish to negotiate with the
nobles, allow me to go in your place.
I know you'd be safe.
You're the king and a great knight,
so the humans couldn't harm
you even if they wanted to.
That's precisely why I should...
You can't.
There's no point in
sending a warrior like you.
This is a matter of appearance.
Our nation needs to see that
even someone who is as powerless
as I can travel amongst the humans
and then safely return home.
That's the point.
Without fear, and with a heart
that's full of trust, I'll go myself.
That's the only way that this can be done.
Be careful, Mother.
Don't go, Mother!
We're the behemoth!
I can't get it.
Where is she going?
My queen.
Trust in me.
Have faith in the woman you
married, and the humans.
You're just the queen of a fish tank.
You arrogant trash!
Goodbye mother.
It's troubling.
Believe me I know how you feel.
But no one can stop her.
All we can do is have faith
and hope for the best.
Your majesty, please be careful out there.
Come home safe.
I love you, mother.
Her children were restless,
awaiting news of her safe return.
In this the island was
united whether we were
royalty or commoners all we
could do was pray for our
queen what a magic box
yeah in the palace it's
called the tamate box to be
exact and it has the power
to make you suddenly grow
older yep well that's
what they say at least so
that means if a kiddo like
the princess opened it
then bam she'd be a full
grown sexy babe lickety split
That would be the idea, sir.
Problem solved!
That is just what I need!
Now I can get married to Shirahoshi
right away and it won't be creepy!
Or so I suspect.
Now!
Go and steal that magic box
thing and steal it quick!
No, wait!
That gate at the palace is
gonna stop us for sure, huh?
I say you just marry her first
and work out the details later.
Yeah, everybody knows you're a creep.
Whoa!
Now there's an idea!
Shirahoshi is pretty cute already.
Even if the box thing doesn't work out,
if I give it ten years or
so, she'll be a knockout.
Yeah, but she's gonna get
even bigger, you know.
Hey!
Different strokes for
different folks, buddy!
I happen to like big women just fine.
Not to mention, she can control the
Sea King, so her powers are big, too.
As big as my ambitions!
She just needs the right man in her life.
And we'll have the whole world
in the palm of our hands!
I'm telling you it's my destiny!
The dream of every decade
since the beginning of time!
Now, let's get started on writing
those wedding invitations, shall we?
You have to propose to her first! Wait!
I don't have any friends!
Days passed with no word from the queen.
The hearts of her people grew heavy.
I really miss hearing her speeches.
Please return safely, Queen Otohime.
Boss, what's wrong?
Why isn't she back?
You think something bad happened?
Keep the faith.
She is fighting to protect
your future, children.
This island's future.
Our hearts are with you, your majesty.
Please come home.
Worry not, my children.
Your mother is a strong and wise woman.
Although it was but a week,
it felt like an eternity.
She's back!
Your Majesty!
I was so worried!
I'm not crying, I just
have something in my eye!
Welcome home!
Your Majesty!
After several days of negotiations,
Queen Otohime was able
to quell the fury of the
celestial dragons and
perhaps more importantly
she brought a piece of
paper back with her that
would prove a beacon of
hope to our entire island.
In truth, it was a greater miracle
than any of us could have imagined.
Everyone, despite our
troubled history with them,
the celestial dragons are very
influential and by meeting with them,
I have been able to bridge a gap.
We may attend the world summit,
yet listen to what they've written to improve
humankind's relationship with fishmen.
We give this petition written by
their queen our full endorsement.
In other words, if we can fill
my petition with signatures,
the world leaders at the
summit will have no choice
but to recognize our right
to be there and furthermore,
our right to be a part
of the surface world.
Finally?
We will see our dream.
I have mixed feelings about
getting support from those guys.
I'm still not sure.
And now, it's in your hands.
We still need more signatures.
I have found the way, but this
is a path we must walk together.
Please, let your cry for freedom be heard.
Only then can we live above
among our human friends.
We've come so far. Please.
Thank you, bud.
Don't get my hopes up.
If you're just going to
change your mind again.
We won't.
My mom said she's gonna sign too.
No offense, Majesty, but I think
you're going to need a much bigger box.
And you better hurry, because the
whole country's going to be lining up.
Don't worry, Your Highness, I
had a feeling this might happen.
Those of you who support our Queen,
put your signatures in here, please!
There's only so much we can
do by ignoring our prejudice.
We need someone like her
to take a step forward.
We can denounce hate, but to
instill hope is a far greater gift.
This is our future-given life,
sooner than we ever imagined.
She can transform this island more
than a life of fighting ever could.
I wish that Arlong understood
that, to save him from hatred.
I wonder, what will he
think of our future?
I wish Tiger were here.
Surely this would have warmed his heart.
It's a dream come true.
Yeah, and your courage made it come true.
Well, I did feel some inspiration.
I felt as if a new road
had been paved for the
future of our people when that
miracle happened. Miracle?
Yes what else could you
call the appearance of
those sea kings that was
nuts think they like us
No Shirahoshi called them here I
don't think it's so strange after
all we can speak to fish Can't
we that's part of what it means
to be merfolk and yet whenever we
try to communicate With the great
sea kings for whatever reason our
words fall on deaf ears no one
on fishman island Can speak to
whales except for your father but
the sea kings well they're beyond
even him they say In a legend
passed down by our family that
every few hundred years a mermaid
will be born into The royal house
with a fearsome power that no one
else on the island possesses the
power to talk to Sea kings and
shirahoshi is the one I believe
she is and according to the rest
of the legend She will meet
someone who will guide both her and
her power in a direction that will
change The world I can't wait to
see oh wow of course if the world
does change then that will likely
mean A change to this island as
well yeah you think it'll help
with the world summon thing you're
Doing perhaps for if it is used
with love her power could save
thousands of lives that is my hope
But who can say it may be
darkness that will rule her heart
instead in that case her power
Could sink the world of course
Shura Hachi is just a child I'm
sure she has no such intentions
But because she is a child
she has yet to understand her
power and cannot control it
If something traumatic were to
happen to her she could unwittingly
cause the sea kings to go
berserk And in great numbers
what then a whole island would be
smashed into itty Betty bits what
the What the heck should we do?
Don't worry.
You can count on me to take
care of her for the time being.
Although, one of these days, the three of
you must become warriors, brave and true.
Then, as warriors and brothers alike,
use your strength to protect
your sister no matter what.
Yeah! But of course!
Thank you.
But even as they made that vow, they could
not have expected what would come next.
Get away! Fire! Fire!
Are we under attack?
What's going on?
Water! Get water! Quick! Put it out!
Who would do such a thing?
We'll lose all of the
signatures at this rate!
Oh, what a shame.
Well, don't mind me.
Nothing suspicious going on here.
Who are you? No one!
Stay away from the princess!
Hey, stop!
Please, someone tell me she's on her own!
Say something!
No, it can't be!
Dammit, no one do such a thing!
We need a doctor.
What's taking so long?
Oh, please!
Answer me, Mother!
Come on, open your eyes!
Whoever did this, I'll make them pay!
Yes, I'm here, Mother.
My little angels, stay by my side.
However you feel, you must remain calm.
I let my guard down.
I was so excited about all of the
signatures, that I failed to protect them.
And look what happened.
Dear Fukaboshi, let me suffer this anger.
Your Majesty, we're here to operate.
Listen.
It doesn't matter who did this to me.
Don't become angry on my behalf.
I don't want that.
Don't submit to resentment.
Don't let hatred get the better
of you in my name or any other.
You...
You can't play, Mother!
Shirahoshi...
Calm yourself.
If something traumatic
were to happen to her,
she could unwittingly cause the Sea Kings
to go berserk, and in great numbers.
Again?
Sweetie, no.
Hey, Joshi, look!
Yeah!
Woo!
Do it the food fish, Mambo, Mambo,
shake it up high, shake it down low.
Mambo, Mambo, dry your tears,
Mambo, Mambo, never fear.
Lucci Hachi!
Do it the food fish, Mambo, Mambo,
shake it up high, shake it down low.
Let's dance along! Yeah!
Don't worry, your brothers will
be here for you wherever you go.
Do-re-mi-fa-so!
The moonfish rubble sure is fun!
Yeah!
It sure is fun, huh?
Do-re-mi-fa-this is so very fun!
Come on!
Do you want to stop?
Why are you doing this?
Get him out of here!
Hurry!
Look, brother, we're happy!
We won't be angry at all,
just like you told us!
It will protect our little sister!
Don't you worry!
Just ask him to make it so much he does!
Stop struggling!
You need to calm down and
get back to the palace!
I swear to you,
the signatures that burned,
I will collect again.
And just like our father, your
sons will become noble warriors.
With all of our strength, we will protect
Shirahoshi and body and spirit alike.
So please, mother, Please.
You need not worry about us.
We are almost there.
Our new home.
In the light of the sun.
There he is!
The shooter's up there!
Go!
Get to the rooftop!
Is he the one?
Where is the Kerr? Boss Jinbei!
One of our men just killed him, sir.
Was it someone we know?
Far from it.
It can't be!
It's a human!
hide the body hold on do what if
this gets out it'll ruin everything
the Queen has accomplished all
of her work will be for nothing
she'll never be able to
rest in peace maybe but
that still doesn't change
the truth does it the
truth is that he was a
lawless pirate pirate or
no pirate all All that
matters is he was human.
Leave it be horny!
Don't do it damn you!
Listen everyone!
It was a human!
A human assassinated our queen!
This is what humans are capable of!
KILLING AND CALL BLIND!
She trusted them with all her heart!
A human.
All she ever wanted was
a peaceful coexistence.
And this human murders her just
when she finally had us convinced.
We put all of our faith in her.
And he's stolen that from us.
By taking Queen Otehime's life.
He's taken our hearts.
And the future of this country.
We could kill you a million times.
And never replace our queen.
You human.
Is there no justice in the world?
What joy can we find now?
It's more than I can take.
All I can see is despair.
All I can see is regret.
Has the king agreed to
leave the tower yet?
Afraid not.
There's no reasoning with him.
He's so stricken with grief and rage.
He's lost all control.
King Neptune.
Lock the door behind me.
and leave it sharp until my
urge to kill Hector Sagan!
Gang Neptune, will you talk to me?
I'm listening.
The shooter was discovered
with the gun still in his hand,
so one of our soldiers killed him.
He was a human.
I would have torn off his limbs
whether he were armed or not.
But my queen would never
have allowed such savagery.
I don't even know when this all began.
But I would only perpetuate
it further by seeking revenge.
If the children of our nation were
to see me engage in such acts?
It would only teach them bitterness.
And show them that rage is the answer.
And this horrible bloodshed
would spiral onward.
It was easy to empathize with
Otohime's message of peace.
So long as it was someone else's problem.
But now?
Why would it be wrong for me to kill
the man who shot my wife to death?
Why is that not my right?
As much as I want to.
I just can't understand that.
In my time as a soldier I took many lives
in reprisal from my fallen comrades.
And I've killed swarms of humans
over the years who besieged us.
But my hypocrisy kept me from
helping Otohime in her endeavors.
So I simply stood by her side and watched.
Why should she die while a beast
like me is allowed to live?
I could never take over her work.
Because my hands are forever stained
with the blood of my brutal history!
My king, we're all teeming
with contradictions.
And we all change with age.
That goes for fishmen and humans alike.
But there are some things that only a
soldier can have the strength to understand.
King Nefk 'un!
Thank you for helping me.
I'm not certain if I'm ready, but at
least I can attend my wife's funeral.
Father, you made it!
I meant you so much!
Shigohoshi.
Father.
My brave sons.
Welcome back.
I'm sorry, children.
I shouldn't have left you alone
during such a terrible time.
You should see this, father.
Hmm?
What is it these letters
keep flying after me no
matter where i go she's
already received five of
them father is this a
love letter sheer is only
six years old who in blazes
is this van der decken
that's the name of a
legendary pirate isn't it
sire my children will
not attend the funeral?
There could be an accomplice still
on the loose for all we know.
Also, I want this sleazy, dick and
character apprehended post-haste! Yes, sir!
My kingdom.
Look up there.
Prince Fukaboshi.
Then he isn't here?
What is he here?
Fuck a bullshit.
In her last moment of life, my mother
happily spoke to us of the future.
We have chosen to adopt our mother's dream
and dedicate our lives
to seeing it through,
no matter how long it takes.
So noble.
We understand that you are not yet
ready, and you likely won't be,
for the World Summit in two years.
But there will be another in six
years, and another after that in ten.
It's only natural for this tragedy to have
reaffirmed your deeply
held mistrust of humans.
So I'll destroy the remaining
signatures that were left unburned.
And together, we'll
start from the beginning.
Someday in our future, when your
wounds have finally begun to heal,
Once you feel you are ready
United We will dream
Of a new life in the sun?